A Guide to the Population Council records, Central Files, Accession 2, RG 2, Series 1 to Series 4 FA432
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 2, Central Files, 1957-1983; bulk; 2; 286 Cubic Feet
  - Subject File, 1951-1981; 4; 85 Cubic Feet 170 boxes: 164 legal document boxes, 4 record cartons, 2 half-legal document box.
    - Basic Book Program, 1969-1977; 1
      - United States - Pennsylvania, 1971-1972 (Box 487, Folder 4572)
      - United States - Texas, 1970-1975 (Box 487, Folder 4573)
      - United States - United Nations - Fund for Population Activities, 1970-1975 (Box 487, Folder 4574)
      - United States - Virginia, 1973-1974 (Box 487, Folder 4575)
      - United States - Washington, 1975 (Box 487, Folder 4576)
      - United States - Washington, D.C., 1969-1975 (Box 487, Folder 4577)
      - United States - Wisconsin, 1970 (Box 487, Folder 4578)
      - Canada, 1970-1972 (Box 487, Folder 4579)
      - USSR, 1969-1975 (Box 487, Folder 4580)
      - Yugoslavia, 1970-1975 (Box 488, Folder 4581)
      - Afghanistan, 1972-1975 (Box 488, Folder 4582)
      - Bangladesh, 1970-1977 (Box 488, Folder 4583-4584)
      - Burma, 1969-1975 (Box 488, Folder 4585)
      - Hong Kong, 1970-1976 (Box 488, Folder 4586)
      - India, 1969-1975 (Box 488, Folder 4587-4589)
      - India, 1969-1975 (Box 489, Folder 4590-4594)
      - Indonesia, 1969-1976 (Box 490, Folder 4595-4599)
      - Indonesia, 1969-1976 (Box 491, Folder 4600-4601)
      - Iran, 1970-1975 (Box 491, Folder 4602)
      - Iraq, 1975 (Box 491, Folder 4603)
      - Israel, 1971-1975 (Box 491, Folder 4604)
      - Japan, 1971 (Box 491, Folder 4605)
      - Jordan, 1971-1975 (Box 491, Folder 4606)
      - Korea, 1969-1975 (Box 491, Folder 4607-4608)
      - Kuwai, 1974 (Box 492, Folder 4609)
      - Lebanon, 1969-1975 (Box 492, Folder 4610)
      - Malaysia, 1970-1975 (Box 492, Folder 4611-4612)
      - Nepal, 1973-1975 (Box 492, Folder 4613)
      - Pakistan, 1970-1975 (Box 492, Folder 4614-4615)
      - Philippines, 1969-1976 (Box 493, Folder 4616-4620)
      - Singapore, 1974-1975 (Box 494, Folder 4621)
      - Sri Lanka (Ceylon), 1969-1975 (Box 494, Folder 4622)
      - Syria, 1971-1974 (Box 494, Folder 4623)
      - Taiwan, 1969-1975 (Box 494, Folder 4624-4625)
      - Thailand, 1969-1975 (Box 494, Folder 4626-4627)
      - Thailand, 1969-1975 (Box 495, Folder 4628)
      - Turkey, 1969-1975 (Box 495, Folder 4629)
      - Vietnam, 1973-1974 (Box 495, Folder 4630)
      - Yemen, Republic of, 1972-1973 (Box 495, Folder 4631)
      - Algeria, 1972-1974 (Box 495, Folder 4632)
      - Botswana, 1973 (Box 495, Folder 4633)
      - South Africa, 1971-1972 (Box 495, Folder 4634)
      - Cameroon, 1971-1974 (Box 495, Folder 4635)
      - Central Africa (Rwanda), 1969 (Box 495, Folder 4636)
      - Chad, 1969 (Box 495, Folder 4637)
      - Dahomey (Benin), 1969 (Box 495, Folder 4638)
      - Egypt, 1969-1975 (Box 495, Folder 4639)
      - Ethiopia, 1969-1975 (Box 495, Folder 4640)
      - Gambia, 1971 (Box 496, Folder 4641)
      - Ghana, 1971-1971 (Box 496, Folder 4642)
      - Ivory Coast, 1973 (Box 496, Folder 4643)
      - Kenya, 1969-1975 (Box 496, Folder 4644)
      - Lesotho, 1970-1975 (Box 496, Folder 4645)
      - Liberia, 1970-1976 (Box 496, Folder 4646)
      - Libya, 1974-1975 (Box 496, Folder 4647)
      - Malawi, 1970-1971 (Box 496, Folder 4648)
      - Mauritius, 1969-1975 (Box 496, Folder 4649)
      - Morocco, 1969-1976 (Box 496, Folder 4650)
      - Mozambique, 1972-1973 (Box 496, Folder 4651)
      - Nigeria, 1970-1975 (Box 497, Folder 4652-4655)
      - Rhodesia, 1974-1975 (Box 497, Folder 4656)
      - Senegal, 1972-1973 (Box 497, Folder 4657)
      - Seychelles, 1975 (Box 497, Folder 4658)
      - Sierra Leone, 1970-1975 (Box 497, Folder 4659)
      - Solami, 1971 (Box 497, Folder 4660)
      - South Africa, 1974-1975 (Box 498, Folder 4661)
      - Sudan, 1972-1975 (Box 498, Folder 4662)
      - Swaziland, 1974-1975 (Box 498, Folder 4663)
      - Tanzania, 1969-1975 (Box 498, Folder 4664)
      - Togo, 1969-1975 (Box 498, Folder 4665)
      - Tunisia, 1969-1975 (Box 498, Folder 4666)
      - Uganda, 1970-1976 (Box 498, Folder 4667)
      - Zaire, 1973-1975 (Box 498, Folder 4668)
      - Zambia, 1971-1975 (Box 498, Folder 4669)
    - Central Files - Microfiche, 1974 (Box 499, Folder 4670)
    - Central Files - Operations, 1973-1976 (Box 499, Folder 4671-4672)
    - Central Files - Procedure Manual, 1974-1976 (Box 499, Folder 4673)
    - Central Files - Records Management Forum, 1974-1976 (Box 499, Folder 4674)
    - Central Files - Reorganization of Council Filing, 1975-1976 (Box 499, Folder 4675-4676)
    - Conference Topics, 1974-1976 (Box 500, Folder 4677-4682)
    - Conference Topics -, 1974 (Box 501, Folder 4683-4685)
    - Conference Topics - United Nations World Population Conference, 1974 (Box 501, Folder 4686-4687)
    - Conference Topics, 1973 (Box 501, Folder 4688)
    - Conference Topics, 1972-1973 (Box 502, Folder 4689-4691)
    - New England Regional Conference - NECORP Book, 1973 (Box 502, Folder 4692)
    - New England Regional Conference - Follow-up, 1972 (Box 502, Folder 4693)
    - New England Regional Conference - Master, 1972 (Box 503, Folder 4694)
    - New England Regional Conference - Preliminary Invitations, 1972 (Box 503, Folder 4695)
    - New England Regional Conference - Site, 1972 (Box 503, Folder 4696)
    - New England Regional Conference - Preliminary, 1972 (Box 503, Folder 4697-4698)
    - New England Regional Conference - Financial, 1972 (Box 503, Folder 4699)
    - New England Regional Conference - Public Information, 1972 (Box 504, Folder 4700)
    - New England Regional Conference - Proceedings - Transcript from Audio Tapes, 1972 (Box 504, Folder 4701-4702)
    - Conference Topics, 1972 (Box 504, Folder 4703-4704, Box 505, Folder 4705-4709)
    - Conference Topics, 1971 (Box 506, Folder 4710-4714)
    - Conference Topics, 1970-1971 (Box 507, Folder 4715-4719)
    - Conference Topics, 1966-1970 (Box 508, Folder 4720-4725)
    - Consultants - Chlodin, Harvey M., 1967 (Box 509, Folder 4726)
    - Consultants - Clemens, George S., 1967-1970 (Box 509, Folder 4727-4728)
    - Consultants - Macisco, John, 1973 (Box 509, Folder 4729)
    - Consultants - Robinson, Ralph R., 1969 (Box 509, Folder 4730)
    - Consultants - Schramm, Wilbur, 1970-1971 (Box 509, Folder 4731)
    - Contraceptive Materials, 1968-1970 (Box 509, Folder 4732)
    - Directory of Contraceptives, 1970 (Box 509, Folder 4733)
    - Cytology, 1968-1970 (Box 509, Folder 4734, Box 510, Folder 4735-4736)
    - Director's Staff Meetings, 1957-1976 (Box 510, Folder 4737-4740, Box 511, Folder 4741-4745)
    - Donors, 1967-1976 (Box 511, Folder 4746-4748, Box 512, Folder 4749-4754)
    - Donors - Prospective, 1973-1975 (Box 512, Folder 4755)
    - Donors - Allen, Vivian B. Foundation, 1969-1971 (Box 512, Folder 4756)
    - Donors - Mauze, Jean, 1968-1974 (Box 513, Folder 4757)
    - Donors - May, Cordelia Scaife, 1967-1974 (Box 513, Folder 4758-4759)
    - Donors - Rockefeller, David Jr., 1967-1970 (Box 513, Folder 4760)
    - Donors - Rockefeller - John D. Jr. (Mrs.), 1961-1969 (Box 513, Folder 4761)
    - Donors - Rockefeller, John D. III, 1969-1974 (Box 513, Folder 4762)
    - Donors - Rockefeller, John D. IV, 1965-1969 (Box 513, Folder 4763)
    - Donors - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1974 (Box 513, Folder 4764)
    - Donors - Rockefeller Foundation, 1974 (Box 513, Folder 4765)
    - Donors - Salisbury Community Foundation (Fred Stanback), 1967-1969 (Box 513, Folder 4766)
    - Donors - Spencer, John, 1967-1970 (Box 513, Folder 4767)
    - President Donor Books - Funds - ICARP, 1964-1976 (Box 513, Folder 4768)
    - President Donor Books - Funds - Individuals, 1964-1976 (Box 514, Folder 4769)
    - President Donor Books - UNFPA - MCH/Family Planning and National Family Planning Programs, 1964-1976 (Box 514, Folder 4770)
    - President Donor Books - Funding - Ford Foundation Special Projects, 1964-1976 (Box 514, Folder 4771-4772)
    - President Donor Books - Funds - ICCR, 1964-1976 (Box 514, Folder 4773-4774)
    - President Donor Books - Funding - Ford Foundation General Purpose, 1964-1976 (Box 515, Folder 4775-4776)
    - President Donor Books - Scaife Family Charitable Funds, 1964-1976 (Box 515, Folder 4777-4778)
    - President Donor Books - Information Office Funds, 1968-1974 (Box 515, Folder 4779-4780)
    - President Donor Books - Funds - Rockefeller Foundation, 1966-1976 (Box 516, Folder 4781-4782)
    - President Donor Books - Ford Foundation Country Grants, 1963-1976 (Box 516, Folder 4783-4784)
    - President Donor Books - Foundation Funds, 1970-1976 (Box 516, Folder 4785-4786)
    - President Donor Books - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Family, 1964-1976 (Box 517, Folder 4787-4788)
    - Family Planning Evaluation Series, 1969-1976 (Box 517, Folder 4789-4790)
    - Family Planning in Industry, 1969-1970 (Box 517, Folder 4791)
    - Films, 1967-1975 (Box 517, Folder 4972-4974, Box 518, Folder 4795-4802)
    - Films - Disney, 1966-1973 (Box 519, Folder 4803-4806)
    - Films - Disney - Lease Forms, 1968-1970 (Box 519, Folder 4807)
    - Films - Disney - Correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box 519, Folder 4808-4809, Box 520, Folder 4810)
    - Films - Disney - 16mm Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 520, Folder 4811)
    - Films - Disney - 16mm Lease and Shipping Notices, 1969 (Box 520, Folder 4812)
    - Films - Disney - Super 8mm Lease and Shipping Notices, 1969 (Box 520, Folder 4813)
    - Films - Disney - Supplementary Production Materials, 1969 (Box 520, Folder 4814)
    - Films - Disney - Lease on PC Prints, 1968 (Box 520, Folder 4815)
    - Films - Disney - Story Development and Production, 1966-1968 (Box 520, Folder 4816-4817)
    - Films - Disney - Production of Translations, 1968 (Box 521, Folder 4818-4821)
      - Spanish Disney Tape (Spanish Test), undated; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1, Reel AV 15832)
        Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - Films - Disney - Carl Nater, 1968-1973 (Box 521, Folder 4822)
    - Films - IUD, 1962-1967 (Box 522, Folder 4823)
    - Films - Japan, 1964 (Box 522, Folder 4824)
    - Films - National Education Television and Radio Center, 1967-1969 (Box 522, Folder 4825)
    - Films - Nexus Films, 1967 (Box 522, Folder 4826)
    - Grant Applications, 1971 (Box 522, Folder 4827)
    - Grant Declination, 1968-1976; 2
      - Anderson, Joseph M., 1975 (Box 522, Folder 4828)
      - Bamberger, Michael, 1973-1975 (Box 522, Folder 4829-4830)
      - Bandes W., Emilio, 1974-1975 (Box 522, Folder 4831)
      - Bean, Lee L., 1975 (Box 522, Folder 4832)
      - Boonlert, Leoprapai, 1974-1975 (Box 522, Folder 4833)
      - Brown, James S., 1974-1975 (Box 522, Folder 4834)
      - Cannon, Kristina B., 1974-1975 (Box 522, Folder 4835)
      - Cargille, Charles M., 1975 (Box 522, Folder 4836)
      - Carrasco de Gomez, Isabel, 1975 (Box 522, Folder 4837)
      - Chaffee, Jeanne Marie Col, 1975 (Box 522, Folder 4838)
      - Cherkaoui, Abdelmalek, 1974 (Box 522, Folder 4839)
      - Clemhoust, Simone, 1974-1975 (Box 522, Folder 4840)
      - Corporacion Centro Regional de Poblacion, 1975-1976 (Box 522, Folder 4841)
      - Correa, Hector, 1974-1975 (Box 523, Folder 4842-4843)
      - Demko, George J., 1976-1977 (Box 523, Folder 4844)
      - DeRoss, Roger M., 1975 (Box 523, Folder 4845)
      - Dobbins, James G., 1974-1975 (Box 523, Folder 4846)
      - Driver, Edwin, 1975-1977 (Box 523, Folder 4847)
      - Edmonston, Barry, 1975 (Box 523, Folder 4848)
      - Etsy, Kathy, 1974-1975 (Box 523, Folder 4849)
      - Farber, Bernard L., 1974-1975 (Box 523, Folder 4850)
      - Friedlander, Dow, 1974 (Box 523, Folder 4851)
      - Fuchs, Ronald J., 1974-1975 (Box 523, Folder 4852)
      - Giao, Nguyen Huy, 1974-1975 (Box 523, Folder 4853)
      - Gomez-Ibanez, Daniel A., 1975 (Box 523, Folder 4854)
      - Gough, Harrison, 1974-1975 (Box 523, Folder 4855)
      - Hartman, Moshe, 1975 (Box 523, Folder 4856)
      - Hirschman, Charles, 1975 (Box 523, Folder 4857)
      - Instituto de Estudios Superiores de Administracion (INESA), 1975 (Box 524, Folder 4858)
      - Instituto Nacional de Ciencias del Comportamiento y de la Actitude, 1975 (Box 524, Folder 4859)
      - Keely, Charles B., 1975 (Box 524, Folder 4860)
      - Kobrin, Frances E., 1974-1975 (Box 524, Folder 4861)
      - LaFerla, John J., 1975 (Box 524, Folder 4862)
      - Linder, Forrest, 1974-1975 (Box 524, Folder 4863)
      - Litchfield, R.B., 1974-1975 (Box 524, Folder 4864)
      - McCabe, James L., 1974-1975 (Box 524, Folder 4865)
      - McIntyre, Robert J., 1974-1975 (Box 524, Folder 4866)
      - MacNeil, Mark K., 1975 (Box 524, Folder 4867)
      - Madigan, Francis C., 1975 (Box 524, Folder 4868)
      - Mani, Srivasa B., 1975 (Box 524, Folder 4868A)
      - Miller, Warren B., 1974-1975 (Box 524, Folder 4869)
      - Mehtabunsia, Ali, 1973-1975 (Box 524, Folder 4870)
      - Michigan, University of, 1973-1975 (Box 524, Folder 4871)
      - Mott, Frank L., 1974-1975 (Box 524, Folder 4872)
      - Mujaju, Akiiki B., 1975 (Box 524, Folder 4873)
      - Murphy, Francis X., 1975 (Box 524, Folder 4874)
      - Nagelschmidt, Anna, 1974-1975 (Box 524, Folder 4875)
      - North Carolina, University of (Chapel Hill), 1974-1975 (Box 524, Folder 4876)
      - Okediji, Peter, 1975 (Box 524, Folder 4877)
      - Okonji, M.O., 1974-1975 (Box 524, Folder 4878)
      - Osterling, Jorge P., 1975 (Box 524, Folder 4879)
      - Peredo Saavedra, Adolfo, 1975 (Box 524, Folder 4880)
      - Rao, G. Ramantha, 1974-1975 (Box 524, Folder 4881)
      - Rawitz, G., 1974-1975 (Box 524, Folder 4882)
      - Reproduction Publication, 1975 (Box 524, Folder 4883)
      - Sabran, Jaques, 1974-1975 (Box 525, Folder 4884)
      - Salkever, Louis R., 1975 (Box 525, Folder 4885)
      - Seiver, Daniel A., 1975 (Box 525, Folder 4886)
      - Shakeel, G. Sabir, 1975 (Box 525, Folder 4887)
      - Semin, G.R., 1974-1975 (Box 525, Folder 4888)
      - Shannon, Lyle W., 1974-1975 (Box 525, Folder 4889)
      - Kalamazoo College, 1970 (Box 535, Folder 4993)
      - Kelly, William J., 1970 (Box 535, Folder 4994)
      - Kent State University, 1970 (Box 535, Folder 4995)
      - Kim, Kyoung-Sik, 1970 (Box 535, Folder 4996)
      - Kim, Yun, 1970-1973 (Box 535, Folder 4997)
      - Klimpel, Felicitas, 1970 (Box 535, Folder 4998)
      - Knights, Peter R., 1970 (Box 535, Folder 4999)
      - Krotki, Karol, 1970-1971 (Box 535, Folder 5000)
      - Krunstadter, Peter, 1969-1970 (Box 535, Folder 5001)
      - LeCavalier, Guy, 1970 (Box 535, Folder 5002)
      - Lee, Nancy Howell, 1970 (Box 535, Folder 5003)
      - Levin, Harry, 1970 (Box 535, Folder 5004)
      - Libutsi, Otanga M., 1969-1970 (Box 535, Folder 5005)
      - Louvain, Universite Cathlique de, 1970 (Box 535, Folder 5006)
      - Marriage Museum, 1970 (Box 535, Folder 5007)
      - Martin, Leroy L. (Mrs.), 1970 (Box 535, Folder 5008)
      - Melbourne, University of, 1969-1970 (Box 535, Folder 5009)
      - Michigan State University, 1970 (Box 535, Folder 5010)
      - Montclair State College, 1970 (Box 535, Folder 5011)
      - Montgomery, Edward, 1970 (Box 535, Folder 5012)
      - Mehta, Surinder K., 1970 (Box 535, Folder 5013)
      - Mourao, Fernando A.A., 1969-1970 (Box 535, Folder 5014)
      - Nam, Charles, 1970 (Box 535, Folder 5015)
      - National Council on Family Relations, 1970 (Box 535, Folder 5016)
      - New Mexico, University of, 1970 (Box 535, Folder 5017)
      - North Carolina, University of, 1970-1975 (Box 535, Folder 5018)
      - Norvell, Douglass G., 1970 (Box 535, Folder 5019)
      - Olsson, Gunnar, 1969-1970 (Box 535, Folder 5020)
      - Opportunities, Inc., 1970 (Box 535, Folder 5021)
      - Ou, Tsuin-Chen, 1970 (Box 535, Folder 5022)
      - Pennsylvania State University, 1970 (Box 535, Folder 5023)
      - Peru, 1969-1970 (Box 536, Folder 5024)
      - Pohlman, Edward, 1970 (Box 536, Folder 5025)
      - Pontifical Gregorian University of Rome, 1969-1970 (Box 536, Folder 5026)
      - Rabie, Hamed A., 1970 (Box 536, Folder 5027)
      - Rakhetla, K.T.J., 1970-1973 (Box 536, Folder 5028)
      - Rao, Sudha, 1970 (Box 536, Folder 5029)
      - Rao, T.R., 1970 (Box 536, Folder 5030)
      - Research Triangle Institute, 1970 (Box 536, Folder 5031)
      - Robbins, Michael C., 1969 (Box 536, Folder 5032)
      - Rohter, Ira, 1970 (Box 536, Folder 5033)
      - Rao, K.N., 1969-1970 (Box 536, Folder 5034)
      - Rothman, Ana Maria, 1970 (Box 536, Folder 5035)
      - Saint Mary's College, 1970 (Box 536, Folder 5036)
      - Senegal, 1968-1970 (Box 536, Folder 5037)
      - Shannon, Lyle W., 1970 (Box 536, Folder 5038)
      - Shiloh, Ailon, 1970 (Box 537, Folder 5039)
      - Shin, Paul Young, 1970 (Box 537, Folder 5040)
      - Shute, Gary, 1970 (Box 537, Folder 5041)
      - Singerman, L.J., 1970 (Box 537, Folder 5042)
      - Sirageldin, Ismail, 1969-1970 (Box 537, Folder 5043)
      - Sposato, Al, 1969-1970 (Box 537, Folder 5044)
      - Sphrehe, J. Timothy, 1969-1970 (Box 537, Folder 5045)
      - Survey Research Center, 1970 (Box 537, Folder 5046)
      - Texas University of (Austin), 1970 (Box 537, Folder 5047)
      - Thailand, 1970 (Box 537, Folder 5048)
      - Timmer, M., 1970 (Box 537, Folder 5049)
      - Tran, Khanh Tuyet, 1970 (Box 537, Folder 5050)
      - Upper Volta, 1969-1970 (Box 537, Folder 5051)
      - Vaidyanathan, K.E., 1970 (Box 537, Folder 5052)
      - Vapnarsky, Cesar A., 1970 (Box 537, Folder 5053)
      - Wallace, Ned, 1970 (Box 537, Folder 5054)
      - Weiss, Brian, 1969-1970 (Box 537, Folder 5055)
      - Weissberg, Joseph, 1970 (Box 537, Folder 5056)
      - Weizmann Institute of Science, 1970-1971 (Box 537, Folder 5057)
      - Weller, Robert H., 1969-1970 (Box 537, Folder 5058)
      - White, Ben, 1970 (Box 537, Folder 5059)
      - White, Martha, 1970-1971 (Box 537, Folder 5060)
      - Winkler, Othmar, 1970 (Box 537, Folder 5061)
      - Woolf, Ralph B., 1970 (Box 537, Folder 5062)
      - Yaukey, David, 1969-1970 (Box 537, Folder 5063)
      - Yen, Y.T., 1970 (Box 537, Folder 5064)
      - Yoon, Jong-Joo, 1970-1975 (Box 537, Folder 5065)
      - Yoshino, Roger I., 1970 (Box 537, Folder 5066)
    - Fertility Trends Project (Burch), 1951-1975; 3
      - Methodology, 1971-1974 (Box 525, Folder 4890-4891)
      - Fact Sheets - Unrevised, undated (Box 526, Folder 4892-4894)
      - Background, undated (Box 526, Folder 4895)
      - Summaries, 1960-1971 (Box 526, Folder 4896)
      - Comments, 1972-1974 (Box 527, Folder 4897-4989)
      - Countries less than 10 Million - Summaries, undated (Box 527, Folder 4899)
      - Bibliography - Fertility, 1973-1974 (Box 527, Folder 4900)
      - Arnold Summary Text, undated (Box 527, Folder 4901)
      - Summary Materials, undated (Box 527, Folder 4902)
      - Draft Text for Chapters 1 and 2, undated (Box 527, Folder 4903)
      - Africa - Drafts which were typed from, 1960-1971 (Box 527, Folder 4904-4905)
      - Asia - First Drafts and Drafts which were typed from, 1960-1972 (Box 528, Folder 4906-4907)
      - Latin America - Drafts which were typed from, 1960-1972 (Box 528, Folder 4908)
      - Fertility Trends Report, 1971-1972 (Box 528, Folder 4909)
      - Countries, undated (Box 528, Folder 4910)
      - Fertility Project, 1971 (Box 528, Folder 4911)
      - Technical Notes, 1971 (Box 528, Folder 4912)
      - Component Impact on CBR - E. Arnold, 1960-1970 (Box 528, Folder 4913)
      - Canada, 1971 (Box 528, Folder 4914)
      - United States, 1971-1972 (Box 528, Folder 4915)
      - Australia, undated (Box 528, Folder 4916)
      - Europe, 1960-1970 (Box 529, Folder 4917)
      - USSR, 1972 (Box 529, Folder 4918)
      - Czechoslovakia, 1961 (Box 529, Folder 4919)
      - Germany, 1964-1969 (Box 529, Folder 4920)
      - Finland, 1960-1968 (Box 529, Folder 4921)
      - France, 1960-1971 (Box 529, Folder 4922)
      - Hungary, 1960-1970 (Box 529, Folder 4923)
      - Netherlands, 1960-1970 (Box 529, Folder 4924)
      - Poland, 1960-1970 (Box 529, Folder 4925)
      - Romania, 1960-1970 (Box 529, Folder 4926)
      - Spain, 1960-1970 (Box 529, Folder 4927)
      - Yugoslavia, 1960-1970 (Box 529, Folder 4928)
      - XRX Fact Sheets - Africa (5 million plus), 1956-1974 (Box 529, Folder 4929)
      - XRX Fact Sheets - Asia (5 million plus), 1969-1974 (Box 529, Folder 4930)
      - XRX Fact Sheets - Latin America (5 million plus), 1960-1974 (Box 529, Folder 4931)
      - Originals of Africa - Drafts, 1956-1974 (Box 529, Folder 4932)
      - Originals of Asia - Drafts, 1960-1974 (Box 530, Folder 4933-4934)
      - Originals of Latin America - Drafts, 1960-1974 (Box 530, Folder 4935-4936)
      - Asia, 1972 (Box 530, Folder 4937)
      - Bangladesh, 1972 (Box 530, Folder 4938)
      - Ceylon, 1953-1970 (Box 530, Folder 4939)
      - China, 1972 (Box 531, Folder 4940)
      - India, 1969-1974 (Box 531, Folder 4941-4943)
      - Indonesia, 1960-1975 (Box 531, Folder 4944)
      - Mayalasia, 1957-1974 (Box 531, Folder 4945)
      - Nepal, undated (Box 531, Folder 4946)
      - Vietnam, 1967-1974 (Box 531, Folder 4947)
      - Pakistan, 1960-1972 (Box 531, Folder 4948)
      - Philippines, 1972-1974 (Box 532, Folder 4949)
      - Singapore, 1972 (Box 532, Folder 4950)
      - South Korea, 1972 (Box 532, Folder 4951)
      - Taiwan, 1961-1972 (Box 532, Folder 4952)
      - Thailand, 1960-1970 (Box 532, Folder 4953)
      - Africa, 1942-1971 (Box 532, Folder 4954)
      - Algeria, 1963-1973 (Box 532, Folder 4955)
      - Congo (Democratic Republic), 1967-1974 (Box 532, Folder 4956)
      - Dahomey, 1961 (Box 532, Folder 4957)
      - Ethiopia, 1966-1971 (Box 532, Folder 4958)
      - Ghana, 1960-1971 (Box 532, Folder 4959)
      - Kenya, 1971 (Box 532, Folder 4960)
      - Malawi, 1956 (Box 532, Folder 4961)
      - Mauritius, 1951-1970 (Box 532, Folder 4962)
      - Morocco, 1955-1962 (Box 533, Folder 4963)
      - Nigeria, 1963-1972 (Box 533, Folder 4964)
      - Senegal, 1956-1963 (Box 533, Folder 4965)
      - South Africa, 1960-1968 (Box 533, Folder 4966)
      - Southern Rhodesia, 1955-1956 (Box 533, Folder 4967)
      - Sudan, 1971-1974 (Box 533, Folder 4968)
      - Tanzania, 1971 (Box 533, Folder 4969)
      - Tunisia, 1955-1968 (Box 533, Folder 4970)
      - Uganda, undated (Box 533, Folder 4971)
      - United Arab Republic, 1971-1975 (Box 533, Folder 4972)
      - Middle East, 1970-1971 (Box 533, Folder 4973-4974)
      - Iran, 1966-1970 (Box 533, Folder 4975)
      - Iraq, 1947-1965 (Box 533, Folder 4976)
      - Israel, 1969-1972 (Box 534, Folder 4977)
      - Jordan, 1972 (Box 534, Folder 4978)
      - Turkey, 1969-1970 (Box 534, Folder 4979)
      - Latin America, 1970-1974 (Box 534, Folder 4980)
      - Argentina, 1972 (Box 534, Folder 4981)
      - Brazil, 1970-1975 (Box 534, Folder 4982)
      - Chile, 1960-1970 (Box 534, Folder 4983)
      - Colombia, 1964-1974 (Box 534, Folder 4984)
      - Costa Rica, 1959-1973 (Box 534, Folder 4985)
      - Cuba, 1970-1974 (Box 534, Folder 4986)
      - Dominican Republic, 1970 (Box 534, Folder 4987)
      - Jamaica, undated (Box 534, Folder 4988)
      - Mexico, undated (Box 534, Folder 4989)
      - Peru, 1972-1974 (Box 534, Folder 4990)
      - Puerto Rico, 1972 (Box 534, Folder 4991)
      - Venezuela, 1972-1974 (Box 534, Folder 4992)
    - Grants - Latin American Listing, 1967-1970 (Box 538, Folder 5067)
    - Grants Proposed, 1962-1974; 4
      - Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 538, Folder 5068)
      - Okonji, M.O., 1974 (Box 538, Folder 5069)
      - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 538, Folder 5070)
      - Wilson, Stuart F., 1973 (Box 538, Folder 5071)
      - Cisneros, Antonio, 1973 (Box 538, Folder 5072)
      - Choldin, Harvey M., 1973 (Box 538, Folder 5073)
      - Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 538, Folder 5074)